# MAYURESH BAILURKAR

# FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER









**+91-7019021346** 

mayureshbailurkar@gmail.com

Belgaum, Karnataka

# SKILLS

- Web Design
- Front End Coding (ReactJS, Redux and CSS, Javascript, Chakra UI)
- Problem-Solving
- Back End Coding (NodeJS, and Express)
- Data structure and Algorithm (DSA)
- GitHub

### **SOFT SKILL**

- Online collaboration
- Remote Work
- Team work

# EDUCATION

#### MASAI SCHOOL

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPMENT Apr-2022

# KLE ENGINEERING COLLEGE, BELGAUM

VITIU

2014 - 2018

## GSS COLLEGE BELGAUM

PUC

2012 - 2014

## EXPERIENCE

## FREELANCING - 3D Visualizer

Oct 2020 - Mar 2021

• Worked closely with designers to create visually appealing and accurate renders.

## PARIKH AND ASSOCIATES - SANGLI

- 3D Visualizer

Dec 2019 - Jul 2020

- Create visual concepts, by hand or using computer software.
- Worked closely with designers to create visually appealing and accurate renders.

# PROFILE

Excellent understanding of frontend and backend programming languages and technology stacks. Demonstrating creativity and analytical skills while completing development, testing, and debugging tasks. Worked with teams to design API and web architecture. Capable of writing production-ready code using ReactJS, Redux, and CSS on the frontend, NodeJS, and Express on the backend.

# PROJECT

## SKINSTORE.COM (CLONE)

#### **Features**

- End-to-End product purchasing flow from the website.
- Login check with (regres.in), Sorting, and Filtering features for products.
- Individual Project completed in 1 week.
- Displaying products added to the cart with details like price, size, quantity, etc.
- The functionality provided to increase the quantity of a product, and changes in price to be displayed under each product and subtotal.
- Executed the Project with pixel-perfect accuracy and provided important functionalities.

#### Tech-Stack

REACT | CSS | JAVASCRIPT | CHAKRA UI

## HIVERH.COM (CLONE)

## Features

- Used Advance CSS and Login check are provided.
- Completed Project in 1 week with a team of 5.

#### Tech-Stack

HTML | CSS | JAVASCRIPT

## Area of Responsibility

- Was responsible for creating 3 service pages using HTML, CSS, and Javascript.
- Executed the pages with pixel-perfect accuracy and functionality.

## SHOP.COM (CLONE) Shop.com is a E-commerce website.

#### **Features**

- End-to-End product purchasing flow from the website.
- Login check, Sorting, and Filtering features for products.
- Completed Project in 1 week with a team of 4.

#### Tech-Stack

HTML | CSS | JAVASCRIPT

## Area of Responsibility

- Was responsible for creating a cart and payment page using HTML, CSS, and Javascript.
- Displaying products added to the cart with details like price, color, size, quantity, etc.
- The functionality provided to increase the quantity of a product, and changes in price to be displayed under each product and subtotal.
- Payment page checks for correct and incorrect credentials (hard-coded).